<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Xiangyong Tan</title>
    <link>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Xiangyong Tan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:27:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://XiangyongTan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>个人简历</title>
      <link>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/cv_chinese/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:27:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/cv_chinese/</guid>
      <description>基本信息  谭祥勇, 男, 重庆开州区人, 1990 年 2 月出生, 上海财经大学统计与管理学院 2016 级博士研究生.  联系方式  邮箱: xiangyongtan@126.com 地址: 上海市国定路 777 号, 上海财经大学统计与管理学院 1302 办公室.  教育经历   2016.09 - 2020.06, 上海财经大学, 统计与管理学院, 博士, 专业: 数理统计学;
  2013.09 - 2016.06, 重庆理工大学, 数学与统计学院, 硕士, 专业: 统计学;
  2009.09 - 2013.06, 重庆师范大学涉外商贸学院, 数学与计算机学院, 学士, 专业: 数学与应用数学 (师范).
  科研项目   主持上海财经大学研究生创新计划项目科研创新基金项目: Expectile 模型下的高维检验. (项目编号: 2017110369);
  参与国家自然科学基金项目: 复杂疾病基因数据的半参数建模及统计推断.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/published_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:25:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/published_paper/</guid>
      <description>Published Papers   Qian, L., Xiangyong, T., and Liming, W. (2019). Testing for error correlation in partially functional linear regression models, Communications in Statistics-Theory and Methods, Accepted.
  Feng L., Pengfei W., Xiangyong, T., Xinmei K. (2018). Short-term analysis and prediction of gold price based on nonparametric autoregression model. Journal of applied statistics and management, 37(2), 357-361.
  Feng L., Xiangyong T.*, Sitong G., Xinmei K., Testing for serial correlation in linear model with validation data, Communications in Statistics-Theory and Methods, 2017, 46(12): 6074-6084.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 17:27:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://XiangyongTan.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Contact Information  Email: xiangyongtan@126.com Address: No. 777, Guoding Rd., Shanghai 200433, China, School of Statistics and Management (Rm. 1302), Shanghai University of Finance and Economics (SUFE)  Education   2016.09 - 2020.06, Shanghai University of Finance and Economics, Statistics, Doctor of Science.
  2013.09 - 2016.06, Chongqing University of Technology, Statistics, Master of Science .
  2009.09 - 2013.06, Chongqing Normal University Foreign Trade and Business College, Mathematics and Applied Mathematics, Bachelor of Science.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>